benchling.com 2015-03-18

# Privacy Policy · Benchling

Benchling Inc. (“Benchling”) operates [Benchling.com](https://benchling.com/). It is Benchling’s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our websites.

#### Website Visitors

Like most website operators, Benchling collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Benchling’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Benchling’s visitors use its website. From time to time, Benchling may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

Benchling also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for users. Benchling only discloses user IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below.

#### Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

Certain visitors to Benchling’s website choose to interact with Benchling in ways that require Benchling to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Benchling gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up for an account at Benchling.com to provide a username and email address. Those who engage in transactions with Benchling are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, Benchling collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with Benchling. Benchling does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

#### Aggregated Statistics

Benchling may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. Benchling may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, Benchling does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

#### Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

Benchling discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on Benchling’s behalf or to provide services available at Benchling’s websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using Benchling’s websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. Benchling will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Benchling discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when Benchling believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Benchling, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of the Benchling website and have supplied your email address, Benchling may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with Benchling and our products. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. Benchling takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

#### Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Benchling uses cookies to help Benchling identify and track visitors, their usage of Benchling’s website, and their website access preferences. Benchling visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Benchling’s website, with the drawback that certain features of Benchling’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

#### Business Transfers

If Benchling, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, or in the unlikely event that Benchling goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of Benchling may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.

#### Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, Benchling may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Benchling’s sole discretion. Benchling encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
